Stay out of the swamp
Hatchet is a comedy, horror film directed by Adam Green.
When a group of tourists on a New Orleans haunted swamp tour find themselves stranded in the
wilderness, their evening of fun and spooks turns into a horrific nightmare.
Ben, played by Joel David Moore.
Marybeth Dunstan, played by Amara Zaragoza.
Marcus, played by Deon Richmond.
Victor Crowley / Thomas Crowley, played by Kane Hodder.
Jenna, played by Joleigh Fioravanti.
Misty, played by Mercedes McNab.
Hatchet is a 2006 American slasher film written and directed by Adam Green.
The film has an ensemble cast, including Joel David Moore, Tamara Feldman, Deon Richmond, Mercedes McNab, Parry Shen, Joleigh
Fioreavanti, Joel Murray, Richard Riehle, Patrika Darbo, Joshua Leonard, Tony Todd, Robert Englund, and Kane Hodder.
The plot follows a group of tourists on a New Orleans haunted swamp tour, who accidentally get stranded in the
wilderness, only to be hunted by a vengeful, supernatural deformed man who kills anyone that enters the swamp.
Hatchet premiered at the Tribeca Film Festival in April 27, 2006, before
releasing in limited theaters domestically on September 7, 2007.
It received mixed reviews from critics, but became
a cult classic among audiences.
The film's successes spawned a film series including three sequels.
A comic book series followed thereafter.
The film explores themes of new orleans, louisiana,
tourist, alligator, male friendship, swamp.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.